{
    "data": {
        "title": "Finnish Flashcards",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "question": "What \"nykyinen\" means",
                    "hint": "Something related to time",
                    "answer": "Current"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What \"arvosana\" means",
                    "hint": "About exams and stuffs",
                    "answer": "Grade"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What \"hakea\" means",
                    "hint": "Something related to application",
                    "answer": "To search"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julkkis means what?",
                    "hint": "You probably want to be that",
                    "answer": "Celebrity"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Meaning of \"maalata\"",
                    "hint": "Most kids like this",
                    "answer": "To paint"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Luento",
                    "hint": "Go to school to take what?",
                    "answer": "Lecture"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Meaning of \"Haaratattelu\"",
                    "hint": "It starts with an \"I\"",
                    "answer": "Interview"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Keksiä means what?",
                    "hint": "It starts with an \"I\"",
                    "answer": "To invent"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Opiskeljavaihto",
                    "hint": "They normally dont study much",
                    "answer": "Exchange student"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Joten",
                    "hint": "It starts with a \"T\"",
                    "answer": "Therefore"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Eronnut",
                    "hint": "Not the best position ever",
                    "answer": "Divorced"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Muisto",
                    "hint": "It starts also with a \"M\"",
                    "answer": "Memory"
                }
            ]
    }
}